<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>simsite</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on simsite</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 02 Sep 2022 18:49:42 +0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Choose Methods</title>
      <link>/online/1-choose_methods/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/online/1-choose_methods/</guid>
      <description> Installation Guide Installation Guide A
devtools::install_github(&amp;quot;duohongrui/simpipe&amp;quot;) B
print(&amp;quot;Hello World!&amp;quot;) [1] &amp;quot;Hello World!&amp;quot; </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Installation</title>
      <link>/programming/1-installation/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/programming/1-installation/</guid>
      <description>Choice1: Installation from Github Choice2: Download Docker Image Install Docker Desktop Download simpipe Docker Image Install simpipe2docker There are two ways to configure programming environment and execute simulation procedure:
install multiple R packages and dependencies from github, it may take 5-30 mins.
install Docker first and download simpipe Docker image from DockerHub. All manipulations in R can be done by a lightweight simpipe2doker package.
Choice1: Installation from Github The first way to configure your programming environment is to install all of the packages and necessary dependencies</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Methods List</title>
      <link>/references/1-methods_list/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/references/1-methods_list/</guid>
      <description>R Markdown Including Plots Methods R Markdown This is an R Markdown document. Markdown is a simple formatting syntax for authoring HTML, PDF, and MS Word documents. For more details on using R Markdown see http://rmarkdown.rstudio.com.
When you click the Knit button a document will be generated that includes both content as well as the output of any embedded R code chunks within the document. You can embed an R code chunk like this:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Splat</title>
      <link>/references/methods/splat/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/references/methods/splat/</guid>
      <description>Estimating parameters from a real dataset Simulating datasets using Splat Datasets with default parameters Determin the number of cells and genes Simulate two or more groups Simulate two or more batches Simulate more groups and batches simutaniously Return results with different format Here Splat method will be demonstrated clearly and hope that this document can help you.
Estimating parameters from a real dataset Before simulating datasets, it is important to estimate some essential parameters from a real dataset in order to make the simulated data more real.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Estimation Parameters</title>
      <link>/programming/2-estimation/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/programming/2-estimation/</guid>
      <description>Estimate Parameters From Local R Step1: Load Packages Step2: Prepare Your Data and Prior Information Step3: Estimate Parameters Estimate Parameters From Docker in R Estimate Parameters By Simpipe Package One dataset ▶️ Multiple Methods Multiple datasets ▶️ Multiple Methods Estimating essential parameters from the real datasets is a necessary step before simulating a new dataset. In this vignette, we demonstrate three ways of performing estimation step, including:
Depend on local R environment Utilize Docker and link Docker and R Special estimation scenarios by Simpipe package Estimate Parameters From Local R Make sure that you have already installed three main packages (simutils, simmethods and simpipe) before doing estimation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Simple</title>
      <link>/references/methods/simple/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/references/methods/simple/</guid>
      <description>Estimating parameters from a real dataset Simulating datasets using Simple Datasets with default parameters Determin the number of cells and genes Here Simple method will be demonstrated clearly and hope that this document can help you.
Estimating parameters from a real dataset Before simulating datasets, it is important to estimate some essential parameters from a real dataset in order to make the simulated data more real. If you do not have a single-cell transcriptomics count matrix now, you can use the data collected in simmethods package by simmethods:data command.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Simulation Online</title>
      <link>/online/2-simulation_online/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/online/2-simulation_online/</guid>
      <description>R Markdown Including Plots R Markdown This is an R Markdown document. Markdown is a simple formatting syntax for authoring HTML, PDF, and MS Word documents. For more details on using R Markdown see http://rmarkdown.rstudio.com.
When you click the Knit button a document will be generated that includes both content as well as the output of any embedded R code chunks within the document. You can embed an R code chunk like this:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kersplat</title>
      <link>/references/methods/kersplat/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/references/methods/kersplat/</guid>
      <description>Estimating parameters from a real dataset Simulating datasets using Kersplat Datasets with default parameters Determin the number of cells and genes Here Kersplat method will be demonstrated clearly and hope that this document can help you.
Estimating parameters from a real dataset Before simulating datasets, it is important to estimate some essential parameters from a real dataset in order to make the simulated data more real. If you do not have a single-cell transcriptomics count matrix now, you can use the data collected in simmethods package by simmethods:data command.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Simulation Datasets</title>
      <link>/programming/3-simulation/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/programming/3-simulation/</guid>
      <description>Simulate Datasets From Local R Step1: Prepare Estimation Results Step2: Check Availabel Parameters Step3: Simulation Simulate Datasets From Docker in R Simulate Datasets By Simpipe Package Generate Multiple Datasets For Every Estimation Result We have already known how to estimate parameters from one or more real datasets and got the estimation results. In this chapter, we will demonstrate how to simulate single-cell transcriptomics data based on the previous estimation results, especially the useful parameters that are usually customized to satisfy the different application situations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Evaluation Datasets</title>
      <link>/programming/4-evaluate_datasets/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/programming/4-evaluate_datasets/</guid>
      <description>R Markdown Including Plots R Markdown This is an R Markdown document. Markdown is a simple formatting syntax for authoring HTML, PDF, and MS Word documents. For more details on using R Markdown see http://rmarkdown.rstudio.com.
When you click the Knit button a document will be generated that includes both content as well as the output of any embedded R code chunks within the document. You can embed an R code chunk like this:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SplatPop</title>
      <link>/references/methods/splatpop/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/references/methods/splatpop/</guid>
      <description>Estimating parameters from a real dataset Simulating datasets using SplatPop Datasets with default parameters Determin the number of cells and genes Simulate two or more groups Simulate two or more batches Simulate more groups and batches simutaniously Here SplatPop method will be demonstrated clearly and hope that this document can help you.
Estimating parameters from a real dataset Before simulating datasets, it is important to estimate some essential parameters from a real dataset in order to make the simulated data more real.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lun</title>
      <link>/references/methods/5-lun/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/references/methods/5-lun/</guid>
      <description>Estimating parameters from a real dataset Simulating datasets using Lun Datasets with default parameters Determin the number of cells and genes Simulate two or more groups Here Lun method will be demonstrated clearly and hope that this document can help you.
Estimating parameters from a real dataset Before simulating datasets, it is important to estimate some essential parameters from a real dataset in order to make the simulated data more real.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lun2</title>
      <link>/references/methods/6-lun2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/references/methods/6-lun2/</guid>
      <description>Estimating parameters from a real dataset Simulating datasets using Lun2 Datasets with default parameters Determin the number of cells and genes Simulate two or more groups Here Lun2 method will be demonstrated clearly and hope that this document can help you.
Estimating parameters from a real dataset Before simulating datasets, it is important to estimate some essential parameters from a real dataset in order to make the simulated data more real.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SCRIP</title>
      <link>/references/methods/7-scrip/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/references/methods/7-scrip/</guid>
      <description>Estimating parameters from a real dataset Simulating datasets using SCRIP Datasets with default parameters Different modes in SCRIP Determin the number of cells and genes Simulate two or more groups Simulate two or more batches Simulate more groups and batches simutaniously Here SCRIP method will be demonstrated clearly and hope that this document can help you.
Estimating parameters from a real dataset Before simulating datasets, it is important to estimate some essential parameters from a real dataset in order to make the simulated data more real.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>powsimR</title>
      <link>/references/methods/8-powsimr/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/references/methods/8-powsimr/</guid>
      <description>Estimating parameters from a real dataset Estimate parameters without ERCC spike-in Estimate parameters with ERCC spike-in Simulating datasets using powsimR Datasets with default parameters Determin the number of cells and genes Simulate two or more groups Simulate two or more batches Simulate more groups and batches simutaniously Here powsimR method will be demonstrated clearly and hope that this document can help you.
Estimating parameters from a real dataset Before simulating datasets, it is important to estimate some essential parameters from a real dataset in order to make the simulated data more real.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>scDD</title>
      <link>/references/methods/10-scdd/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/references/methods/10-scdd/</guid>
      <description>Estimating parameters from a real dataset Simulating datasets using scDD Datasets with default parameters Determin the number of cells Here scDD method will be demonstrated clearly and hope that this document can help you.
Estimating parameters from a real dataset Before simulating datasets, it is important to estimate some essential parameters from a real dataset in order to make the simulated data more real. If you do not have a single-cell transcriptomics count matrix now, you can use the data collected in simmethods package by simmethods:data command.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>scDesign</title>
      <link>/references/methods/11-scdesign/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/references/methods/11-scdesign/</guid>
      <description>Simulating datasets using scDesign Datasets with default parameters Determin the number of cells Simulate two or more groups Here scDesign method will be demonstrated clearly and hope that this document can help you.
Simulating datasets using scDesign There is no estimation step when using scDesign, so we can directly simulate new datasets through reference data.
library(simmethods) library(SingleCellExperiment) # Load data ref_data &amp;lt;- simmethods::data We will simulate a dataset based on refernece data with different scenarios.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>scDesign2</title>
      <link>/references/methods/12-scdesign2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/references/methods/12-scdesign2/</guid>
      <description>Estimating parameters from a real dataset Default estimation Information of cell groups Information of cell types Simulating datasets using scDesign2 Datasets with default parameters Determin the number of cells Simulate two or more groups Here scDesign2 method will be demonstrated clearly and hope that this document can help you.
Estimating parameters from a real dataset Before simulating datasets, it is important to estimate some essential parameters from a real dataset in order to make the simulated data more real.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>zinbwave</title>
      <link>/references/methods/13-zinbwave/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/references/methods/13-zinbwave/</guid>
      <description>Estimating parameters from a real dataset Simulating datasets using zinbwave Here zinbwave method will be demonstrated clearly and hope that this document can help you.
Estimating parameters from a real dataset Before simulating datasets, it is important to estimate some essential parameters from a real dataset in order to make the simulated data more real. If you do not have a single-cell transcriptomics count matrix now, you can use the data collected in simmethods package by simmethods:data command.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>zingeR</title>
      <link>/references/methods/14-zinger/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/references/methods/14-zinger/</guid>
      <description>Estimating parameters from a real dataset Simulating datasets using zingeR Datasets with default parameters Determin the number of cells and genes Simulate two groups Here zingeR method will be demonstrated clearly and hope that this document can help you.
Estimating parameters from a real dataset Before simulating datasets, it is important to estimate some essential parameters from a real dataset in order to make the simulated data more real. If you do not have a single-cell transcriptomics count matrix now, you can use the data collected in simmethods package by simmethods:data command.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>zinbwaveZinger</title>
      <link>/references/methods/15-zinbwavezinger/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/references/methods/15-zinbwavezinger/</guid>
      <description>Estimating parameters from a real dataset Simulating datasets using zinbwaveZinger Datasets with default parameters Determin the number of cells and genes Simulate two groups Here zinbwaveZinger method will be demonstrated clearly and hope that this document can help you.
Estimating parameters from a real dataset Before simulating datasets, it is important to estimate some essential parameters from a real dataset in order to make the simulated data more real. If you do not have a single-cell transcriptomics count matrix now, you can use the data collected in simmethods package by simmethods:data command.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SPARSim</title>
      <link>/references/methods/18-sparsim/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/references/methods/18-sparsim/</guid>
      <description>Estimating parameters from a real dataset Estimation without cell group information Estimation with cell group information Estimation with spike-in genes Simulating datasets using SPARSim Datasets with default parameters Simulate groups Simulate batch Here SPARSim method will be demonstrated clearly and hope that this document can help you.
Estimating parameters from a real dataset Before simulating datasets, it is important to estimate some essential parameters from a real dataset in order to make the simulated data more real.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SPsimSeq</title>
      <link>/references/methods/19-spsimseq/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/references/methods/19-spsimseq/</guid>
      <description>Simulating datasets using SPsimSeq Datasets with default parameters Determin the number of cells and genes Simulate groups Simulate batches There is no individual estimation step using SPsimSeq as the estimation is combined with simulation step.
library(simmethods) library(SingleCellExperiment) # Load data ref_data &amp;lt;- simmethods::data Simulating datasets using SPsimSeq Datasets with default parameters Determin the number of cells and genes Simulate groups Simulate batches Datasets with default parameters The reference data contains 160 cells and 4000 genes, if we simulate datasets with default parameters and then we will obtain a new data which has the same size as the reference data.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ESCO</title>
      <link>/references/methods/20-esco/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/references/methods/20-esco/</guid>
      <description>Estimating parameters from a real dataset Simulating datasets using ESCO Datasets with default parameters Determin the number of cells and genes Simulate two or more groups Here ESCO method will be demonstrated clearly and hope that this document can help you.
Estimating parameters from a real dataset Before simulating datasets, it is important to estimate some essential parameters from a real dataset in order to make the simulated data more real.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SparseDC</title>
      <link>/references/methods/21-sparsedc/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/references/methods/21-sparsedc/</guid>
      <description>Estimating parameters from a real dataset Simulating datasets using SparseDC Datasets with default parameters Determin the number of cells and genes Simulate two or more groups Here SparseDC method will be demonstrated clearly and hope that this document can help you.
Estimating parameters from a real dataset Before simulating datasets, it is important to estimate some essential parameters from a real dataset in order to make the simulated data more real.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>muscat</title>
      <link>/references/methods/22-muscat/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/references/methods/22-muscat/</guid>
      <description>Estimating parameters from a real dataset Default eatimation Estimation with cell groups Simulating datasets using muscat Datasets with default parameters Determin the number of cells and genes Simulate two or more groups Here muscat method will be demonstrated clearly and hope that this document can help you.
Estimating parameters from a real dataset Before simulating datasets, it is important to estimate some essential parameters from a real dataset in order to make the simulated data more real.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>hierarchicell</title>
      <link>/references/methods/23-hierarchicell/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/references/methods/23-hierarchicell/</guid>
      <description>Estimating parameters from a real dataset Simulating datasets using hierarchicell Datasets with default parameters Determin the number of cells and genes Here hierarchicell method will be demonstrated clearly and hope that this document can help you.
Estimating parameters from a real dataset Before simulating datasets, it is important to estimate some essential parameters from a real dataset in order to make the simulated data more real.
library(simmethods) library(SingleCellExperiment) # Load data set.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>dropsim</title>
      <link>/references/methods/24-dropsim/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/references/methods/24-dropsim/</guid>
      <description>Estimating parameters from a real dataset Simulating datasets using dropsim Datasets with default parameters Determin the number of cells and genes Here dropsim method will be demonstrated clearly and hope that this document can help you.
Estimating parameters from a real dataset Before simulating datasets, it is important to estimate some essential parameters from a real dataset in order to make the simulated data more real.
library(simmethods) library(SingleCellExperiment) # Load data ref_data &amp;lt;- simmethods::data estimate_result &amp;lt;- simmethods::dropsim_estimation( ref_data = ref_data, verbose = T, seed = 10 ) # Estimating parameters using dropsim Simulating datasets using dropsim After estimating parameter from a real dataset, we will simulate a dataset based on the learned parameters with different scenarios.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PROSSTT</title>
      <link>/references/methods/26-prosstt/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/references/methods/26-prosstt/</guid>
      <description>Estimating parameters from a real dataset Simulating datasets with cell trajectory using PROSSTT Datasets with default parameters Determin the number of cells and genes Visualization Here PROSSTT method will be demonstrated clearly and hope that this document can help you.
Estimating parameters from a real dataset Before simulating datasets, it is important to estimate some essential parameters from a real dataset in order to make the simulated data more real.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TedSim</title>
      <link>/references/methods/27-tedsim/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/references/methods/27-tedsim/</guid>
      <description>Estimating parameters from a real dataset Simulating datasets with cell trajectory using TedSim Datasets with default parameters Determin the number of cells and genes Visualization Here TedSim method will be demonstrated clearly and hope that this document can help you.
Estimating parameters from a real dataset Before simulating datasets, it is important to estimate some essential parameters from a real dataset in order to make the simulated data more real.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>dyntoy</title>
      <link>/references/methods/28-dyntoy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/references/methods/28-dyntoy/</guid>
      <description>Estimating parameters from a real dataset Simulating datasets with cell trajectory using dyntoy Datasets with default parameters Determin the number of cells and genes Visualization Here dyntoy method will be demonstrated clearly and hope that this document can help you.
Estimating parameters from a real dataset Before simulating datasets, it is important to estimate some essential parameters from a real dataset in order to make the simulated data more real.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SymSim</title>
      <link>/references/methods/30-symsim/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/references/methods/30-symsim/</guid>
      <description>Estimating parameters from a real dataset Simulating datasets with cell trajectory using SymSim Datasets with default parameters Determin the number of cells and genes Visualization Here SymSim method will be demonstrated clearly and hope that this document can help you.
Estimating parameters from a real dataset Before simulating datasets, it is important to estimate some essential parameters from a real dataset in order to make the simulated data more real.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>VeloSim</title>
      <link>/references/methods/31-velosim/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/references/methods/31-velosim/</guid>
      <description>Estimating parameters from a real dataset Simulating datasets with cell trajectory using VeloSim Datasets with default parameters Determin the number of cells and genes Visualization Here VeloSim method will be demonstrated clearly and hope that this document can help you.
Estimating parameters from a real dataset Before simulating datasets, it is important to estimate some essential parameters from a real dataset in order to make the simulated data more real.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MFA</title>
      <link>/references/methods/32-mfa/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/references/methods/32-mfa/</guid>
      <description>Estimating parameters from a real dataset Simulating datasets with cell trajectory using MFA Datasets with default parameters Determin the number of cells and genes Visualization Here MFA method will be demonstrated clearly and hope that this document can help you.
Estimating parameters from a real dataset Before simulating datasets, it is important to estimate some essential parameters from a real dataset in order to make the simulated data more real.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>phenopath</title>
      <link>/references/methods/33-phenopath/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/references/methods/33-phenopath/</guid>
      <description>Estimating parameters from a real dataset Simulating datasets with cell trajectory using phenopath Datasets with default parameters Determin the number of cells and genes Visualization Here phenopath method will be demonstrated clearly and hope that this document can help you.
Estimating parameters from a real dataset Before simulating datasets, it is important to estimate some essential parameters from a real dataset in order to make the simulated data more real.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
