<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Programming Usage on simsite</title>
    <link>/programming/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Programming Usage on simsite</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 01 Sep 2022 20:22:45 +0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/programming/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Installation</title>
      <link>/programming/1-installation/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/programming/1-installation/</guid>
      <description>Choice1: Installation from Github Choice2: Download Docker Image Install Docker Desktop Download simpipe Docker Image Install simpipe2docker There are two ways to configure programming environment and execute simulation procedure:
install multiple R packages and dependencies from github, it may take 5-30 mins.
install Docker first and download simpipe Docker image from DockerHub. All manipulations in R can be done by a lightweight simpipe2doker package.
Choice1: Installation from Github The first way to configure your programming environment is to install all of the packages and necessary dependencies</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Estimation Parameters</title>
      <link>/programming/2-estimation/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/programming/2-estimation/</guid>
      <description>Estimate Parameters From Local R Step1: Load Packages Step2: Prepare Your Data and Prior Information Step3: Estimate Parameters Estimate Parameters From Docker in R Estimate Parameters By Simpipe Package One dataset ▶️ Multiple Methods Multiple datasets ▶️ Multiple Methods Estimating essential parameters from the real datasets is a necessary step before simulating a new dataset. In this vignette, we demonstrate three ways of performing estimation step, including:
Depend on local R environment Utilize Docker and link Docker and R Special estimation scenarios by Simpipe package Estimate Parameters From Local R Make sure that you have already installed three main packages (simutils, simmethods and simpipe) before doing estimation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Data Simulation</title>
      <link>/programming/3-simulation/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/programming/3-simulation/</guid>
      <description>Simulate Datasets From Local R Step1: Prepare Estimation Results Step2: Check Availabel Parameters Step3: Simulation Simulate Datasets From Docker in R Simulate Datasets By Simpipe Package Generate Multiple Datasets For Every Estimation Result We have already known how to estimate parameters from one or more real datasets and got the estimation results. In this chapter, we will demonstrate how to simulate single-cell transcriptomics data based on the previous estimation results, especially the useful parameters that are usually customized to satisfy the different application situations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Data Assessment</title>
      <link>/programming/4-evaluate_datasets/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/programming/4-evaluate_datasets/</guid>
      <description>Evaluate the simulated cell groups Simulate the dataset with cell groups Prepare the labels of cell groups Assess the simulated cell groups Evaluate the simulated DEGs Simulate the dataset with specified proportion of DEGs Prepare the information of DEGs Assess the validity of the simulated DEGs The situation where more than two groups are simulated Evaluate the simulated cell batches Simulate the dataset with cell batches Prepare the information of cell batches Assess the simulated cell batches Evaluate the simulated trajectories Simulate the dataset with cellular trajectory Assess the simulated trajectory After obtaining the simulated datasets and corresponding information of cells and genes, we can assess the simulation output with the cell or gene information.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
